<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>There must be a better software</title>
    <description>Thoughts on better software by JohnNy_cz</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 22:25:06 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 22:25:06 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>There must be a better software</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The title of this article is a lie. It’s not always true that there “must” be better software. There’s always a lot of compromise in software. I don’t just mean the classial triangle of time - quality - number of features. Software reflects different ideas by many people involved in its design. If software was a cake, there would often be fruit, cream, cucumbers and meat in it. Because somebody wasn’t always on board with the idea of making a cake, so we threw some meat in. Software is a compromise, and a compromise means that there is no winner who takes it all, and so better quality is not always what is actually desired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the title of this post is a lie, but it suggests what I would like to write about on this blog: software and its quality. Very often quality of software suffers and it’s not because of admitted compromises, but because writing good quality software is a skill that one person can probably never fully master. It takes a lot of time; it requires an open mind; it requires changing your views very frequently; it requires rejecting ideas that seemed great just a few moments ago. It is hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a lot of techniques and tools to write better software, but then there’s also a certain mindset that helps thinking about software, making better decisions about software and therefore actually writing better software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides this I would also like to write about my personal experiences related to writing software.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 21:06:25 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/software/blog/2016/07/11/there-must-be-a-better-software.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/software/blog/2016/07/11/there-must-be-a-better-software.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>software</category>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
